{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 360,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(95\\frac{33}{100}\\) &minus; \\(6775\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(6870\\frac{33}{100}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-4.511\\) + \\(366.7\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(362.189\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-5.57\\) &minus; \\(5851\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(5845\\frac{43}{100}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-9.195\\) &minus; \\(\\dfrac{2262}{5}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(-461\\frac{119}{200}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\dfrac{3497}{50}\\) &minus; \\(3464\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(-3394\\frac{3}{50}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.014\\) &div; \\(\\dfrac{4}{5}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{400}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(27\\frac{11}{25}\\) + \\(3644\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(3671.44\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(-9\\frac{421}{500}\\) and \\(\\dfrac{2547}{50}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(-9\\frac{421}{500} > \\dfrac{2547}{50}\\)",
        "\\(-9\\frac{421}{500} < \\dfrac{2547}{50}\\)",
        "\\(-9\\frac{421}{500} = \\dfrac{2547}{50}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(6\\frac{219}{500}\\) and \\(61.64\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(6\\frac{219}{500} > 61.64\\)",
        "\\(6\\frac{219}{500} < 61.64\\)",
        "\\(6\\frac{219}{500} = 61.64\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(398\\) &times; \\(\\dfrac{78}{125}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(248\\frac{44}{125}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the result of \\(0.8\\) &div; \\(1.5\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.533",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(\\dfrac{7447}{1000}\\) and \\(484\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(\\dfrac{7447}{1000} > 484\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{7447}{1000} < 484\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{7447}{1000} = 484\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the result of \\(-0.07\\) &div; \\(-15\\) to 0 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.15\\) &div; \\(10\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{200}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the result of \\(0\\) &div; \\(0.08\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(231\\frac{1}{10}\\) &minus; \\(6\\frac{271}{1000}\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(224.829\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(9\\) &div; \\(0.07\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(128\\frac{4}{7}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-292\\) &times; \\(690\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(201480\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(66.91\\) + \\(749.1\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(816.01\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(\\dfrac{16}{5}\\) and \\(909\\frac{1}{5}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(\\dfrac{16}{5} > 909\\frac{1}{5}\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{16}{5} < 909\\frac{1}{5}\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{16}{5} = 909\\frac{1}{5}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(91\\frac{91}{100}\\) + \\(286\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(377.91\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(1\\) &times; \\(-0.571\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(-0.571\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(9.899\\) and \\(\\dfrac{1}{10}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(9.899 > \\dfrac{1}{10}\\)",
        "\\(9.899 < \\dfrac{1}{10}\\)",
        "\\(9.899 = \\dfrac{1}{10}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(704\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(495616\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.847\\) &times; \\(65.9\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(55.8173\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(1\\) &div; \\(-0.2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(5\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(4430\\) + \\(83.81\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(4513\\frac{81}{100}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\dfrac{961}{200}\\) + \\(4623\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(4627\\frac{161}{200}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(\\dfrac{-2343}{100}\\) and \\(101\\frac{3}{5}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(\\dfrac{-2343}{100} > 101\\frac{3}{5}\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{-2343}{100} < 101\\frac{3}{5}\\)",
        "\\(\\dfrac{-2343}{100} = 101\\frac{3}{5}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(588\\) &times; \\(\\dfrac{299}{1000}\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(175.812\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(53.85\\) and \\(-46.67\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(53.85 > -46.67\\)",
        "\\(53.85 < -46.67\\)",
        "\\(53.85 = -46.67\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-0.06\\) &div; \\(9\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{150}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(76.89\\) &minus; \\(-52.03\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(128\\frac{23}{25}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(254\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(64516\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-9262\\) + \\(6\\frac{337}{500}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(-9255\\frac{163}{500}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(20.64\\) + \\(966\\frac{3}{10}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(986\\frac{47}{50}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(664.6\\) &minus; \\(\\dfrac{1411}{1000}\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(663.189\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(\\dfrac{517}{1000}\\right)^2\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(0.267289\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(627.6\\) + \\(-9.294\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(618\\frac{153}{500}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(4.75\\) and \\(1\\frac{1}{2}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(4.75 > 1\\frac{1}{2}\\)",
        "\\(4.75 < 1\\frac{1}{2}\\)",
        "\\(4.75 = 1\\frac{1}{2}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.1\\) &div; \\(0\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(\\dfrac{-61}{500}\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{3721}{250000}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(\\dfrac{123}{50}\\right)^2\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(6.0516\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-755\\) &times; \\(\\dfrac{-919}{1000}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(693\\frac{169}{200}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(\\dfrac{188}{5}\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(1413\\frac{19}{25}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(3466\\) and \\(478.4\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(3466 > 478.4\\)",
        "\\(3466 < 478.4\\)",
        "\\(3466 = 478.4\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.03\\) of \\(0.598\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(0.01794\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\dfrac{-4489}{10}\\) &minus; \\(3178\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(-3626.9\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(994.6\\) + \\(-0.631\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(993\\frac{969}{1000}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(0.792\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{9801}{15625}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(0.57\\right)^2\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{3249}{10000}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\dfrac{353}{1000}\\) &times; \\(\\dfrac{387}{5}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(27\\frac{1611}{5000}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(-81.6\\right)^2\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(6658.56\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(\\left(\\dfrac{-363}{50}\\right)^2\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(52.7076\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about \\(51\\frac{6}{25}\\) and \\(637\\frac{9}{10}\\)?",
      "choices": [
        "\\(51\\frac{6}{25} > 637\\frac{9}{10}\\)",
        "\\(51\\frac{6}{25} < 637\\frac{9}{10}\\)",
        "\\(51\\frac{6}{25} = 637\\frac{9}{10}\\)"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(-0.935\\) &times; \\(1.57\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(-1.46795\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(21\\) of \\(125\\) as a decimal expansion",
      "answer": "\\(2625\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(8424\\) &minus; \\(484.5\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(7939\\frac{1}{2}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(0.016\\) &div; \\(-1.4\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{175}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Compute \\(58.22\\) &minus; \\(6\\frac{553}{1000}\\) as a mixed/proper fraction",
      "answer": "\\(51\\frac{667}{1000}\\)",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    }
  ]
}